* Problem statement *
When you connect with a new person online, you need to exchange a number of contact methods like 
1. Phone number for call/SMS
2. Number for Whatsapp/Telegram (In case its a different phone number)
3. EMail ID (sometimes official, sometimes personal)
4. Twitter Handle
5. Website URL (company or personal)
6. Facebook ID
... and so on

Everytime the senders need to mentally decide what level of connectivity info to give and then trade these.. 

After giving/receiving these the user has to manually take actions like adding number of phone book, sending request on facebook, adding email id to address book, following the person on twitter etc

* Solution suggestion *
A mobile app - UnivID

The idea is to have an app which will help up encode the information we want to send to the other person such that he received UnivID which his app will decode and take necessary actions like adding to phone book, sending request, bookmarking in browser etc.

The app can have plugins for future services such that if WeChat is added, the app would know how to add contact in WeChat

The UnivID will be signed in such a way that only the receiver can decode it and if forwarded to others will fail to decode.

There can be stock UnivID (e.g. Business UnivID) which can be picked and sent or specific UnivID which can be created for different individuals
